[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Live Forever]
[Episode 19]
Manager Qing Yuan.
I brought you some fruit.
Long time no see.
Princess Ningjia.
Qiu.
Answer the phone.
Answer the phone!
I brought you some files about people who live forever.
What's wrong?
Qiu is in danger.
You're awake.
Does your head hurt?
Are you still dizzy?
Has it been a long time
since you felt your life slipping away?
You will keep bleeding.
Ning Changyue will catch a cold and get sick.
So falling in love really can undo the Vow to Live Forever.
Princess Ningjia can live forever,
as long as the heavens.
Yet you gave it all up
for a guard.
Since you don't cherish it,
I'll grant your wish.
This
is the palace dungeon from 3,000 years ago,
the place you and that guard
desperately wanted to leave.
How about this?
I'll bury you here today.
Okay?
Who exactly are you?
Servant Liu Yi
pays respects to Your Highness,
Princess Ningjia.
No wonder we could never find you.
I don't know what dark magic you used
to turn yourself into such a lingering
half-human, half-ghost monster.
Monster?
Aren't you the same?
Do you think all methods of living forever
are as easy and costless
as yours?
I relied on the vengeful spirits
of all the dead medicine slaves in Southern Qin,
suffering the pain of shedding my skin and being reborn every hundred years
just to barely survive. Yet you…
You thief who stole the Tree Spirit of Immortality.
You enjoy its blessings,
yet you squander the power of living forever like this.
What does our vow to live forever
have to do with you?
What does it have to do with me?
What do you mean by "What does it have to do with me"?
It was me
who searched through all the ancient texts and visited all the famous mountains.
It was me who tested the blood of all the medicine slaves.
It was also me
who had General Yu lock up the Tree Spirit
in the darksteel cage.
Once the elixir was refined,
I would have taken it before that cursed emperor
to achieve an immortal and indestructible body.
My plan was flawless.
It was you.
It was you
who ruined everything!
Answer the phone.
Okay, thank you.
The auction house said,
next, they'll send over
all the information of Qing Yuan.
We'll definitely find a way to locate them.
Where are you?
Why didn't you answer the phone?
Guard Ning,
I hope you've been well.
Actually,
Mr. Ning,
are you looking for any collectibles lately?
Let Qiu go.
If you want someone, take me.
It's been 3,000 years.
You're still so self-righteous.
Your princess
is enjoying the mortal cycle of birth, aging, illness, and death.
But what a pity.
Her stolen blood of immortality
doesn't seem to withstand much bleeding.
In just a short while,
her face turned as pale as paper.
Your Highness,
do you have any last words
for your beloved guard?
Princess. Guard.
Do you really think this is the Southern Qin palace?
You wretched eunuch.
Your Highness,
you're as annoying as ever.
But if
I make a few cuts on her body,
will she still be
so stubborn?
Don't touch her!
Or I'll make you pay!
What?
Want to find her?
Don't you long-lived ones
have a way to meet each other quickly?
Once you're dead,
you'll find her soon enough.
It's just that
the power of living forever is fading.
If you die this time,
you might really die.
No, no.
Ning Changyue, no!
Calm down!
Lin Huai.
Listen to me.
As long as I die,
she'll appear by my side immediately.
She'll be safe.
This is the only way!
Come back!
And then what?
You died.
Even if she escapes this time,
can she escape the next time?
Liu Yi just wants to watch you
seek your own doom again and again.
Ning Changyue,
think carefully.
You two have been together for 3,000 years.
How many times have you died
and lived together to get to where you are today?
If you die today,
will Liu Yi let her off?
I'm asking someone
to track the location of Song Yiqiu's phone,
but it takes time.
Think quickly now.
Is there any place that is special
for you and Song Yiqiu?
He has planned this for so long.
He couldn't have just picked a random place.
Red light!
Where is she?
I must have missed something.
Do you really think this is the Southern Qin palace?
You wretched eunuch.
The Southern Qin palace.
What?
The place where the Vow to Live Forever and Liu Yi's power began.
It's also the place where our feud began.
After so long,
your Guard Ning
hasn't said he would sacrifice his life
to save you.
Then he will never find this place.
What a pity.
Your love
isn't that everlasting after all.
So much for loving each other forever.
So much for never parting.
In the end,
you only care about yourselves.
You're deceiving yourselves.
Love
isn't only real if you die
for each other.
Our love
is just about wanting to live well
with each other.
So what if you've lived for thousands of years?
In the end,
you don't understand the meaning of love at all.
This broken immortality of yours
makes you nothing but a walking corpse.
What do you know?
I have love.
I love my younger sister.
My younger sister
could have lived forever with me.
Take this identity token
and go out through the west corner gate.
Everything Lord Ning arranged is still in effect.
Because you two
took away the immortality that belonged to her.
Xiaoyuan.
You are Xiaoyuan's older brother.
You are actually Xiaoyuan's older brother.
Have mercy, my lord!
I can't leave the palace.
I can't leave!
Your Highness,
I am doing this willingly.
I entered the palace
to look for my long-lost brother.
For now,
my brother is still missing.
I can't leave.
Lord Ning helped me.
His wish is to help you escape the palace.
I will also escape during the chaos.
Hurry.
No.
Your Highness.
After you escape,
the world is vast.
Your Highness, I hope
you get what you wish for.
I didn't expect
that Xiaoyuan was sent by her own brother
to be a blood-testing medicine slave.
She could have been free,
but she chose to stay in the palace voluntarily,
just for…
For…
For what?
♪ Always secretly guessing ♪
Just for reuniting with you.
♪ Always wondering who's looking ♪
Xiaoyuan came looking for me?
No.
♪ The evil still quietly approaches ♪
I didn't mean to kill Xiaoyuan.
I didn't mean to.
It was you
who let the princess go?
You are all sinners.
Give me back
my immortality.
Brother.
Xiaoyuan.
What?
You killed her?
It was you who killed her!
How could you
kill your own sister?
She only wanted to reunite with you.
She just wanted to find you.
No.
It's not like that.
She deserved to die.
Xiaoyuan deserved to die.
She deserved to die in the first place.
It's all because of you.
It's you.
♪ So here is to you ♪
♪ My darling ♪
♪ And here is to you ♪
♪ My friend ♪
♪ Here is to you ♪
♪ My lover ♪
♪ I'll follow you until the end ♪
Qiu.
Here.
Slow down.
♪ I'll follow you until ♪
Qiu.
Are you okay?
Where did he hurt you?
I'm fine.
Are you okay?
Why wouldn't I be?
Here.
Let me take a look.
I'm fine.
Qiu.
We are both safe now.
Let's go.
Let's go home.